Narrator: Part 3
Host: OK, Team B, now you have 30 seconds to ask Mike questions.
But remember: Mike can only answer Yes or No.
Alice: Hello, Mike.
Do you wear a uniform or special clothes?
Mike: Yes, I do.
Not a uniform, but special clothes.
George: Do you have special qualifications?
Mike: Yes, I do.
Charlie: Do you work on a team?
Mike: No.
But sometimes other people help me.
Host: Remember, Mike, you can only answer Yes or No.
Mike: Oh, yes. Sorry.
Alice: Do you work inside?
Mike: Yes, I do.
George: Do you work on the weekend?
Mike: No, I don’t.
Charlie: Do you like your job?
Mike: Yes, I love it.
But people don’t always like me!
Host: Thank you, Mike.
So, Team B, is Mike a hair stylist, a dentist, or a chef?
You have one minute.